Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 6, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 91: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 33 Aug. 13
  - Item 92: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 32 Aug. 6
  - Item 93: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 30 July 23
  - Item 94: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 34 Aug. 20
  - Item 95: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 35 Aug 27
  - Item 96: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 29 July 16
  - Item 97: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 28 July 9
  - Item 98: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 27 July 2
  - Item 99: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 26 June 25
  - Item 100: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 25 June 18
  - Item 101: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 16 April 16
  - Item 102: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 17 April 23
  - Item 103: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 18 April 30
  - Item 104: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 21 May 21
  - Item 105: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 22 May 28
  - Item 106: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 20 May 14
  - Item 107: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 23 June 4
  - Item 108: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 24 June 11
  - Item 109: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 18 April 29
  - Item 110: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 17 April 22
  - Item 111: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 16 April 21
  - Item 112: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 15 April 15
  - Item 113: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 14 April 8
  - Item 114: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 13 April 1
  - Item 115: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol.3, No. 12 March 25
  - Item 116: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 6 Feb. 11
  - Item 117: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 118: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 7 Feb. 18
  - Item 119: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 3 Jan. 21
  - Item 120: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 52 Dec. 31
  - Item 121: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 1 Jan. 7
  - Item 122: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 2 Jan. 14
  - Item 123: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 4 Jan. 28
  - Item 124: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 5 Feb. 4
  - Item 125: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 15 April 9
  - Item 126: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 14 April 2
  - Item 127: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 47 Nov. 19
  - Item 128: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 44 Oct. 29
  - Item 129: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 45 Nov. 5
  - Item 130: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 48 Nov. 26
  - Item 131: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 46 Nov. 12
  - Item 132: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 50 Dec. 10
  - Item 133: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 49 Dec. 3
  - Item 134: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 51 Dec. 17
  - Item 135: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 23 June 3
  - Item 136: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 20 May 13
  - Item 137: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 19 May 6
  - Item 138: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No.22 May 27
  - Item 139: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 10 March 11
  - Item 140: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 14 March 18
  - Item 141: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 8 Feb. 26
  - Item 142: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 9 March 4
  - Item 143: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 21 May 20
- Box: 6, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 47 Nov. 18
  - Item 2: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 46 Nov. 11
  - Item 3: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 51 Dec. 16
  - Item 4: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 52 Dec. 22
  - Item 5: News Brief, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 32 Aug. 5
  - Item 6: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 44 Oct. 28
  - Item 7: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 45 Nov. 4
  - Item 8: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 4 Jan. 27
  - Item 9: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 43 Oct. 21
  - Item 10: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No.3 Jan. 20
  - Item 11: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 2 Jan. 13
  - Item 12: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 50 Dec. 9
  - Item 13: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 49 Dec. 2
  - Item 14: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 48 Nov. 25
  - Item 15: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 44 Nov.4
  - Item 16: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 45 Nov. 11
  - Item 17: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 47 Nov. 24
  - Item 18: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 46 Nov. 18
  - Item 19: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Author: Detroit Edison Company
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 49 Dec. 9
  - Item 20: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 48 Dec. 2
  - Item 21: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 3 Jan. 20
  - Item 22: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 50 Dec. 16
  - Item 23: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 2 Jan. 13
  - Item 24: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 4 Jan. 27
  - Item 25: Supervisor News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 7 Feb. 17
  - Item 26: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 8 Feb. 24
  - Item 27: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 6 Feb. 10
  - Item 28: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 5 Feb. 3
  - Item 29: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 9 March 2
  - Item 30: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 11 March 16
  - Item 31: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 10 March 9
  - Item 32: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 13 March 13
  - Item 33: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 12 March 23
  - Item 34: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 14 April 6
  - Item 35: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Item 36: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 15 April 13
  - Item 37: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 16 April 20
  - Item 38: Nes Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 22 June 1
  - Item 39: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 27 July 6
  - Item 40: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 20 May 18
  - Item 41: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 33 Aug. 17
  - Item 42: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol.5, No. 24 June 15
  - Item 43: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 23 June 8
  - Item 44: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 25 June 22
  - Item 45: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 21 May 25
  - Item 46: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 30 July 27
  - Item 47: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 31 Aug. 3
  - Item 48: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 26 June 29
  - Item 49: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 32 Aug. 10
  - Item 50: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 19 May 11
  - Item 51: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 35 Aug. 31
  - Item 52: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 36 Sept. 7
  - Item 53: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 37 Sept. 14
  - Item 54: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 38 Sept. 21
  - Item 55: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 34 Aug. 24
  - Item 56: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 29 July 20
  - Item 57: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 39 Sept. 28
  - Item 58: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 40 Oct. 5
  - Item 59: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 42 Oct. 19
  - Item 60: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 41 Oct. 12
  - Item 61: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 5 Oct. 26
  - Item 62: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 28 July 13
  - Item 63: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 44 Nov.2
  - Item 64: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 46 Nov. 16
  - Item 65: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol 5, No. 45 Nov. 9
  - Item 66: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 48 Dec. 7
  - Item 67: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 47 Nov. 30
  - Item 68: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 49 Dec. 14
  - Item 69: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 2 Jan. 10
  - Item 70: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 1 Jan. 4
  - Item 71: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 5 Feb. 1
  - Item 72: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 6 Feb. 8
  - Item 73: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 7 Feb. 15
  - Item 74: News Briefs, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 50 Dec. 20
  - Item 75: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 11 March 15
  - Item 76: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Item 77: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 8 Feb. 22
  - Item 78: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 9 March 1
  - Item 79: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 12 March 22
  - Item 80: News Briefs, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 13 March 29
  - Item 81: Synchroscope: It's a Matter of Degrees!, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Item 82: Today, 1975; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 33 Dec. 17 2 copies
- Box: 6, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Supervisor News, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: July 22
  - Item 2: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: July 30
  - Item 3: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 21
  - Item 6: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 23
  - Item 7: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: July 14
  - Item 8: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: July 1
  - Item 9: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 10: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Oct. 14
  - Item 11: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 12: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 24
  - Item 13: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 14: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 18
  - Item 15: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 16: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: May 13
  - Item 17: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 6
  - Item 18: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: March 9
  - Item 19: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 20: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 9
  - Item 21: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Aug. 18
  - Item 22: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Aug. 11
  - Item 23: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 5
  - Item 24: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 29
  - Item 25: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 26: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 27: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 28: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 3
  - Item 29: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 4
  - Item 30: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 29
  - Item 31: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 12
  - Item 32: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: July 18
  - Item 33: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: July 15
  - Item 34: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: July 31
  - Item 35: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 36: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Aug. 7
  - Item 37: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 13
  - Item 38: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Dec. 31
  - Item 39: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 40: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Feb. 16
  - Item 41: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 42: Supervisor News, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 43: Supervisor News, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 24
  - Item 44: Supervisor News, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 25
  - Item 45: Supervisor News, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 46: Supervisor News, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 2
  - Item 47: Supervisor News, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 27
  - Item 48: Supervisor News, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Feb. 8
  - Item 49: Supervisor News, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Dec. 6
  - Item 50: Suprevisor News, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 9
  - Item 51: Supervisor News, 1966; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Feb. 15
  - Item 52: Supervisor News, 1966; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Feb. 10
  - Item 53: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: March 10
  - Item 54: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 21
  - Item 55: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 56: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 22
  - Item 57: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 13
  - Item 58: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Jan. 14
  - Item 59: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Dec. 29
  - Item 60: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Feb. 4
  - Item 61: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Feb. 12
  - Item 62: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: May 29
  - Item 63: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: May 20
  - Item 64: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 25
  - Item 65: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 66: Supervisor News, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Nov. 27
  - Item 67: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 68: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 69: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Dec. 10
  - Item 70: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Dec. 3
  - Item 71: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 72: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Nov. 24
  - Item 73: Supervisor News, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 74: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Author: http://youtu.be/jpHePXBf060
  - Item 75: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: May 12
  - Item 76: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: May 8
  - Item 77: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Nov. 16
  - Item 78: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 79: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Oct. 15
  - Item 80: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Oct. 29
  - Item 81: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 82: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Oct. 2
  - Item 83: Supervisor News, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Notes: Oct. 13